"Black Vinegar Private Middle School”
Man, what a surprise.
I guess there are espers
other than you, Shigeo.
But it looks like he's
pretty surprised himself.
Impossible...
Are you a natural?
There's another like me?
What is the creepy-looking
ball of energy next to you?
What?
Are you its master?
No, it's haunting me.
Well, whatever.
There are a bunch of questions
I want to ask you,
but before that,
we need to establish something...
The hierarchy here.
Say what?
"Progress Toward Mob's Explosion: 45%"
"Progress Toward Mob's Explosion: 47%"
If everyone is not special
Maybe you can be what you want to be
We'll be able to find our answers
1%, 2%, 3%, 4%, 5%, 6%, 7%, 8%, 9%, 10%...
11%, 12%, 13%, 14%, 15%,
16%, 17%, 18%, 19%, 20%...
21%, 22%, 23%, 24%, 25%...
Admiration, troubles, pump up
26%, 27%, 28%, 29%, 30%...
Searching for yourself, telepathy
31%, 32%, 33%, 34%, 35%...
Asking for the impossible, psycho punch
36%, 37%, 38%, 39%, 40%...
Youthful Salt Splash
Mob? Mob? What do you want?
Mob? Mob? Why do you want?
Mob? Mob? Who do you want?
Move! Move! Just like Mob!
If everyone is not special
Maybe you can be what you want to be
Even if you hold onto happiness and sadness
Your life is your own, OK?
It's OK you are not special
We'll all be able to find our answers
81%, 82%, 83%, 84%, 85%,
86%, 87%, 88%, 89%, 90%...
91%, 92%, 93%, 94%, 95%,
96%, 97%, 98%, 99%...
"Mob Psycho 100" 91%, 92%, 93%,
94%, 95%, 96%, 97%, 98%, 99%...
91%, 92%, 93%, 94%, 95%,
96%, 97%, 98%, 99%...
"OCHIMUSHA"
" ~Psychic Powers and Me~"
Be careful just in case, Shigeo.
Even you could get tripped up
if you're not care--
Sorry, I wasn't listening.
What?!
Why are you attacking me?
I haven't done anything.
Let's be...
He's on guard.
Not that I don't understand how he feels.
I bet he's lived his life so far
as the big fish in a very small pond.
And for the first time ever, he's meeting
someone that could be his natural enemy.
If he doesn't establish
his superiority right now,
he won't be satisfied, I'm sure.
But, that aside...
What's with those weird movements?
They're kinda like wire action.
Telekinesis.
It lets you move objects around, and stuff.
You're not gonna do it?
I get nauseous, so no.
I use telekinesis to teleport
close to my opponent
and blow him away with my Psycho Fist.
This dancing strategy that I've perfected
to use against average people
apparently looks like nothing more
than weird movements against him.
Damn it!
Shigeo, you need to teach him a lesson here.
Show him who's boss.
Come on. Look at how he's standing.
He's gonna attack again.
You need to hit him
with something big, too.
No. You're not supposed to use
psychic powers against people.
You idiot! Look at who you're talking about!
He's put his psychic powers to good use
and is living a fulfilling life!
And then look at you.
You live a dull lifestyle,
with one boring day after another.
Do you think there's anything appealing
about you without your psychic powers?
Listen up!
We were born with special powers
that other people don't have,
but we mustn't let it get to our heads
and think we're special.
People who are fast,
"39th Choral Competition"
people who sing well,
people who are book smart,
people who are good at talking,
and people who can use psychic powers...
You can't put one over the other.
Being confident about your powers is fine,
but you mustn't get conceited.
Depending on how we use our powers,
they can also be deadly weapons.
They're just like knives.
What are you not
supposed to do with knives?
Point them at people?
So you do get it.
Make sure you never forget that.
That's the moral code people like us
with special powers need to live by.
That all gets ruined
once you know Reigen said it.
Anyway, I won't use them in a fight.
Also, I don't want to live a life
having to rely on psychic powers.
I'm going to find
some other potential within me.
Not to mention, I started working out.
I'm going to change.
You say that, but...
--Shigeo!
--How about that?!
That was a telekinetic tackle
with all my weight behind it.
A life without using psychic powers?
How stupid!
There's no reason to live your life
stooping to the level of average people!
Other potentials are absolutely useless!
Working out? Studying?
Leave all that crap to the average people!
Brain, brawn, and even the law
are all powerless before my gift!
I'm special, and the world
revolves around me!
Jeez, I guess there's no choice.
Hey, little boy. How about
we just call this a draw?
Not happening.
Ending up in a draw with a guy like that
would be the biggest disgrace in my life.
I can't have you breaking Shigeo, either.
He has no intention of fighting back,
so he's obviously going to lose.
That... wouldn't be good.
Dimple?
Most of my spiritual power's been erased,
so I'm pretty much just
some scraps left over, but...
Even then, I shouldn't have any problems
disciplining a cocky little brat.
Shigeo's a man who can become a god.
He's not a second-rate loser like--
Huh?
Dimple!
I erased that thing with my Psycho Wave.
From the core, so there wouldn't
be a single shred left.
Dimple's been exorcised...
"Progress Toward Mob's Explosion: 47%"
"Progress Toward Mob's Explosion: 50%"
Forget about your club.
Work on your psychic powers instead!
Tsubomi-chan, eh? She's got a nice ass.
Who the hell are you calling a ladybug?!
I'm gonna send your master to the hospital.
I'll make you popular.
Hey! Want me to show you
how to use X-ray vision?
I don't know either, you perv!
Just for a sec, would you
let me take over your body?
Dimple...
What? Are you so shocked
that your pet was erased?
Not really.
"Progress Toward Mob's Explosion: 50%"
Yeah, I guess you wouldn't be...
After all, it was sort of a pointless
existence to begin with.
Though that goes for you, too.
Compared to me, you're third-rate.
Nothing but small fry.
You can become big! I guarantee it!
Some idiots get the wrong idea
if things aren't spelled out for them.
They think they can be someone
if they actually try.
Be more confident, Shigeo!
After all, you're the main character!
What? What's with that look?
Hey, why do you have to belittle others
by calling them average or small fry?
Wha...?
Well, I just realized that he might
actually have been an okay guy, that's all...
Compared to you.
What?
Don't...
...think that you can keep that
smug look on your face forever!
I'll make you submit to me
with my psychic powers!
I'm gonna come at you
with full power and no brakes!
That's dangerous.
If it wasn't me, you could hurt someone.
Stop that.
Are you trying to say
that you won't get hurt?
Quit underestimating my powers!
What's wrong? You just going
to keep defending yourself?
I told you to stop that.
Show me your powers!
If you're not going
to show me your powers,
I guess we'll have to try something else.
I'll just see how much you can take
by administering an endurance test.
Ow.
The home ec room.
Knives are dangerous.
You shouldn't point--
Don't order me around.
You'll reduce your lifespan that way.
Of course, I have no intention
of killing him,
but I'm sure he'll feel
like fighting back now.
Will you stop? This is going
to cause an accident.
Huh?
You did this on purpose, didn't you?
A huge accident has occurred.
I'm going to kill you!
"Top of Teru's Head 0%"
"Mob Psycho 100"
You'll pay for this.
I won't forgive you, even if you apologize!
You...
You totally thought I look even more
like an ochimusha now, didn't you?
Huh? I didn't say that.
So you did think it.
No, that's fine. I'll admit it.
This shameful sight! This truth!
And I'll acknowledge you, too.
What's your name?
Kageyama... Kageyama Shigeo.
Kageyama... I'm Hanazawa.
Hanazawa Teruki.
Hi, Hanazawa-kun. Nice to meet you.
No, not as a friend.
I acknowledged you as an enemy.
By doing that, I can get
even more serious about this.
S-Stop this already.
If you want to stop this, make me stop!
Come on, come on, come on! What's wrong?
Fight back, or you'll wind up badly hurt!
You're dealing with me!
I'm popular, and the
main character of the world!
Everything revolves around me!
Hanazawa Teruki is the chosen one!
Why? How can you be
so confident in yourself?
What a stupid question!
It's because I have psychic powers!
It's the power to control all!
And you are my first enemy!
Now, attack me!
Let's have a test of strength!
No.
Why?! I'm telling you that it's okay!
Because... I don't want to
injure you really badly.
Wha--?
What a funny joke!
Don't compare me to those average people.
I'm on a completely different level
than them as living creatures.
Being able to use
psychic powers isn't that...
--What?
--Oh, well, I just thought you were going a bit overboard.
You're the only person
who could make that argument.
That's why you're an eyesore!
Oh, I just realized why you
hold such animosity toward me.
You don't like me because we're the same.
You're sort of like me, Hanazawa-kun...
Not the fact that we both
have psychic powers,
but the fact that you have
no confidence in yourself, just like me.
If you take away your psychic powers,
there'll be nothing left.
You'll be empty.
You're scared of that realization.
No friends, and no standing out.
Just another average loser
who won't leave a mark.
That's me.
Deep down, you're the same as me.
You just don't want to admit that you're
nothing without your psychic powers--
No!
Quit dreaming! The two of us
are completely different!
We're the same.
From my perspective,
you're totally average.
Shut up!
He's not using his powers...
What am I doing? How did this happen?
Damn it, it's you! This is all your fault!
Everything was perfect.
Teru-kun, you got another perfect score?
As long as I used my powers,
--everything went
exactly how I wanted it to go.
--What was that shot? That was amazing!
--everything went exactly how I wanted it to go.
We're sorry! Please forgive us!
And yet, you took my world...
U-Um... I made some cookies,
if you'd like some.
You... Your existence...
...destroyed that!
Damn it!
Use them! Use your psychic powers!
No...
I can't use them...
--...against people!
--Is he coming?!
What the heck was that?
Just how much are you going
to keep rejecting me?
Hey, Kageyama. Didn't you say
that you started working out?
That means that no matter how hard
you try, that's all you've got.
People can't change that easily.
Just give it up. Use your psychic powers.
Otherwise, I'm going to...
Give it back!
Give us back our New Year's money!
Don't get so cocky, brat. I'll kill you.
--Ritsu!
--You stay out of this!
Nii-san!
Nii-sa...
It hurts, Nii-san...
I'm going to change.
I won't use them.
Huh? Hey, Kageyama?
Hey... Hey! Wake up!
Wait! Don't leave me behind!
Kageyama...
Kageyama Shigeo and Hanazawa Teruki.
The battle between these two espers
never reached its conclusion.
As a result of rejecting each other's ideals,
there was no victor,
and they were only left with a feeling
of emptiness deep in their hearts.
Or so it seemed...
What... is that?
Do you finally feel like fighting?
Good! In the end, you couldn't
stay true to your ideals, either!
Bring it! Ultimate Barrier!
You used them! Kageyama!
You finally couldn't stand it anymore
and used your psychic powers!
You used them against another person!
Huh?
Is he unconscious?
Then what the hell is this power?
What...?
My powers are being
sucked in by Kageyama...
No, that's not all... All of
the energy in the atmosphere...
Are you telling me his vessel
is able to handle this much?
Teru sensed in there something
that must never be touched.
Something incomparable,
its identity unknown.
You're kidding...
What in the world did I awaken?
That's enough! I'm sorry!
I won't use my psychic powers
against other people!
Oh, I guess...
...I'm actually just an average person...
It didn't take long for Mob to realize.
He failed to change.
He caused another accident
because of his psychic powers.
He didn't know
where to direct his emotions.
He was overwhelmed, his powerlessness
born from contradictions.
The feeling that he would never
be able to conquer himself...
Sadness.
This was Mob's meager attempt
at resistance towards himself.
Hanazawa-kun, um...
--I'm sorry about your clothes an--
--W-Wait! Kageyama, I'm...
Ow... What happened with the fight?
It's Teru-san! He's right over there.
Huh? What the hell?
He's been brutally executed!
I-I'm not gonna let that happen to my hair!
Those guys...
You just saw it, Kageyama.
It's just as you said...
--If you take away our psychic powers...
--Kageyama-kun!
Ah, guys...
Hey, Kageyama, are you hurt?
I'm fine.
All right, then, good.
We're gonna go back and do more squats!
There's nothing I can even say.
I completely lost.
"Under Construction"
Mob searched for about three hours,
but he couldn't find Dimple.
I'm home.
Nii-san?
Welcome home. You're gonna catch a cold.
Thanks.
You're home late today. Do you want to eat?
Nah. I'm gonna head to bed.
You seem down. Did something happen?
If you need to talk,
I'll be happy to listen. Good night.
Ritsu.
I'm sorry about that one time.
That one time?
You mean when you got carsick and
threw up into the hood of my jacket?
No... Well, I'm sorry about that, too.
I really can't remember what happened
with that accident
involving my psychic powers.
What... did I do to you back then?
Oh, you mean when those
high school kids picked a fight with us.
You didn't do anything to me, Nii-san.
One of the punks
kicked me away, and I got hurt.
But you protected me, Nii-san.
You should get over it already. Good night.
Today, after 5 PM,
countless people have reported seeing
a supernatural phenomenon in
the stormy skies above Seasoning City.
"(An ochimusha) was flying!" a supernatural
phenomenon in the stormy skies above Seasoning City.
"(An ochimusha) was flying!"
Among the rubble,
"(An ochimusha) was flying!" there were also reports
of what looked like a person flying up into the air,
there were also reports of what looked
like a person flying up into the air,
--Back then...
--but we have not been able to confirm any victims or their well-being.
--Ritsu!
--You stay out of this!
Nii-san!
"A Supernatural Phenomenon in the Skies Above
Seasoning City!?" "Footage Submitted by a Viewer"
"A Supernatural Phenomenon in the Skies Above Seasoning City!?" "Footage
Submitted by a Viewer" The theory that this was man-made is gaining traction.
The theory that this was
man-made is gaining traction.
That wasn't Nii-san.
I have no appetite.
He caught a cold.
We, who live at the corner of the world
Will get beyond our tears
and head towards the light.
The dreams and ideals that we believe in
Feel like they may shatter
as soon as we take our eyes off them
Thousands, millions of distinct Flashbacks
Underneath the sky in slow motion,
So real that I want it to disappear.
My heart was stolen
a second before the unpredictable,
After being hurt on a whim
something from somewhere
is overflowing and won't stop.
We, who live at the corner of the world
Will get beyond our tears
and head towards the light
Zero, or One? Ten, or Hundred?
We're looking for the answer.
But over and over again
The sound in our hearts resonates together
"Yes n "No n
His overwhelming desire for psychic powers
makes Ritsu-kun stray from the right path.
Having no idea that was happening,
Mob goes on a carefree date with Tome.
Hey, now, Mob. This isn't the time for that!
Next time on Mob Psycho 100 Episode 6:
"Discord
- To Become One~."
First-press limited edition?
That is the absolute best decision.
"Discord” "~To Become One~" First-press limited
edition? That is the absolute best decision.